<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IDecided</string>
    <string name="but1">The Descartes Square</string>
    <string name="but2">Balance Sheet</string>
    <string name="but3">Coin</string>
    <string name="but4">The Wheel of Fortune</string>
    <string name="but5">The Tarot Card Layout</string>
    <string name="but6">1d20</string>
    <string name="but7">About</string>
    <string name="butRu">RU</string>
    <string name="butEng">ENG</string>
    <string name="home"><u>home</u></string>
    <string name="close"><u>close</u></string>
    <string name="infoMenu1">Answer 4 questions sequentially, setting the importance level for each of the reasons, and the app will calculate the most profitable solution to your problem!</string>
    <string name="infoMenu2">Enter the pros and cons of your solution sequentially, setting the importance level for each item, and the app will calculate the most profitable solution to your problem!</string>
    <string name="infoMenu3">Don\'t know what decision to make? Flip a coin!</string>
    <string name="infoMenu4">Spin the wheel of solutions and trust Lady Fortune!</string>
    <string name="infoMenu5">Nothing could be better than relying on a map drawn by an unknown artist with an abundance of surreal symbols. But... Maybe this particular card will change your life?</string>
    <string name="infoMenu6">Roll a twenty-sided dice from DND for good luck!</string>
    <string name="infoMenu7">Here is information about us</string>
    <string name="fortunaH">Your prediction for today:</string>
    <string name="infoOut1">Clearly...</string>
    <string name="infoOut2">I get it.</string>
    <string name="infoOut3">Great!</string>
    <string name="fortuna1">The Deities themselves bestow blessings on you in all your worldly affairs!  But, as we know, success in life depends only on your capabilities and diligence, and not on external circumstances.  Go ahead! Throw yourself into the pool and work hard, unpredictable capitalist heights await you!</string>
    <string name="fortuna2">Enjoy all the delights of instability. They come to you to remind you that life is not only about cool successes, but also the art of suffering and making life difficult for yourself and others.  Enjoy every moment of disorder and become a master of chaos and anarchy!</string>
    <string name="fortuna3">When your problems are not being solved, nothing can be better than to sit and dream of a better future instead of doing something. Dive deeper into your dream world and allow yourself to enjoy the endless path of self-deception and fruitless fantasies.</string>
    <string name="fortuna4">Burn bridges, cut off opportunities and burn the brightest! Have fun with emotional breakdowns with your whole being and be content with the crumbs left after the flame.</string>
    <string name="fortuna5">Open your eyes and you will see important things: the water will be wet, the fire will be hot, and the snow will be white. Try to look at all this from a different angle and maybe you will find your truth in wine.</string>
    <string name="fortuna6">Put on your superhero cape and no one will be able to stop you! And don\'t forget that random symbols in the drawing are the most reliable way to deal with all the problems.</string>
    <string name="fortuna7">Just look at this message and all your problems will simply disappear into thin air! So believe in yourself and allow yourself to go to the top of success.</string>
    <string name="fortuna8">Just read this text and immediately become the best version of yourself! The only question is how much effort and time you are willing to invest in order to achieve the desired result. And the symbols in the drawing are just a reminder that our fate depends on ourselves, not on magic wheels.</string>
    <string name="butFortuna">TWIST</string>
    <string name="butMoney">DROP IT OFF</string>
    <string name="butTaro">PULL</string>
    <string name="butDnd">THROW IT</string>
    <string name="taro1">It symbolizes control, willpower, determination, success, action — how impressive! We all know that with these qualities, anyone can achieve anything! But the inverted version: lack of control, opposition, lack of direction and self—discipline - this is, of course, a real art. It is better to sit back than to embark on an exhausting restructuring of oneself and the development of personal qualities! Feel this motivation, ambition and control! But be careful not to lose your way: life is such a bore without a healthy dose of fear and doubt!</string>
    <string name="taro2">It symbolizes the so-called "thoughtful sitting on the floor", where thoughts devour you from the inside, and the price for your arrogance knocks on the door.
 The awakening? Rebirth? Its all too lofty.
 Lets just admit that we are all victims of our own illusions, especially when it comes to mistakes that seem to have been forgotten for a long time, but are always being revived like annoying advertisements.  Now is the perfect time to think about whether your actions are consistent with your values or are they just a smelly compromise?
 A question from Dostoevsky: are you a trembling creature or do you have the right?! Take the time to get to know yourself before turning on that "running man" mode again.  And dont forget that "You made your own wheel.
And I made a runner squirrel costume for myself
So that 24 hours a day
Chasing a ghostly prize with all your might" - Noize MC</string>
    <string name="taro3">This card perfectly symbolizes that all good things come to an end, and you are right in line for psychotherapy. Renewal, awareness, is just a way to switch channels when your life starts to resemble a broken record. A powerful movement? Just try not to end up with the usual "two steps forward, three steps back." The Death Card is like a mockery of fate: yes, one chapter ends, but do not rush to remove the old notes — they will still be needed when you start to stir up failures over and over again. And it\'s up to you to decide which page will be next - a new chapter? Good stability? Or just a new batch of old rusty junk?</string>
    <string name="taro4">How cozy it is to be trapped! Any addiction and depression is, in fact, a paradise for lazy minds, where negative thinking becomes a lifestyle. Betrayal? Pf, just another touch to the portrait of the sufferer. The devil is your best friend, isn\'t he? Although you\'re supposed to be in control of your life, he\'s happy to tell you your habits. Even sports and social media turn into his insidious tentacles if you do not follow the measure. But don\'t lose heart! The main thing is to keep a sense of humor and redirect your desires to something more important, such as choosing the volume of your suffering.</string>
    <string name="taro5">You have an authority figure, a father figure. This person has excellent control over his emotions and is trustworthy. He himself does not miss the opportunity to demonstrate "masculine energy", representing an exemplary fatherly figure. Hooray, your butt can sleep peacefully on the sofa, because your father is looming over us. And the fact that he may not be what you dreamed of is that you made this choice in the first place.</string>
    <string name="taro6">The Empress with the crown seems to hint: look for beauty and happiness in your life. But it seems that she forgot to clarify that for this search you may have to throw feathers on your head and wave a magic wand to at least catch something. Keep looking, dear ones! Suddenly, behind the coincidence of coincidences, there will be that same spark of joy in the very depths of your overgrown soul.</string>
    <string name="taro7">Fate, fate and karma are just the perfect cocktail for those who like to sit on the couch and wait for luck to knock on your door. If this card falls out, consider yourself lucky! If you believe in fate, it\'s great, if you don\'t, it\'s also great. Listen to your psychic abilities – or just your intuition, if you are not too sophisticated in esotericism. However, "Just remember, no matter how much you do, what\'s next - the world will always find where to throw you an older rope" - Asper X
                         Make your dreams come true, as if you have the strength to do so, and you have protectors in heaven. Remember, there is nothing to be afraid of – everything will go on as usual thanks to divine intervention and a secret plan that no one knows about.</string>
    <string name="taro8">Letting go of a situation, sacrifice, pause for thought, insecurity, spiritual development… Oh, what comforting terms to describe our stay in the center of his Majesty\'s Stagnation! How nice it is to know that in this short moment we are standing on the threshold of enlightenment, waiting for an epiphany to finally hit us and spit out the abyss of introspection. The Hanged Man is that magical "waiting card" where time stops and we make a good face at a bad game. We may not enjoy this limbo, but who would turn down the opportunity to sit around drinking the elixir of fear of life? After all, isn\'t it wonderful to sacrifice your dreams and connections by staying put?</string>
    <string name="taro9">You are a noble seeker of wisdom who hides in the caves of his thoughts, hoping to find some soul-stirring truth there. Privacy? Yes, of course, when you don\'t know how to say "I\'m lonely" without a poetic touch. And the spiritual enlightenment that comes from spitting at the ceiling for a long time, because what could be more enlightening than endless contemplation of dust? The hermit is just a joke of nature! It symbolizes the wisdom gained by meeting with the most distant and no less lonely corners of your soul. The motto of this card is: "The closer to yourself, the further away from the whole world!" It is very convenient, by the way! But do you really need it?</string>
    <string name="taro10">The fool symbolizes the very optimism that, with its inherent naivety, walks through life as if on green lawns on a rainbow, not realizing at all that a swamp can hide behind every rainbow. Every day for such a person is a tricky adventure with a constant happy ending, as if he pulled a lucky ticket out of a magician\'s hat. And those who believe that "rose-colored glasses" will somehow prevent difficulties from coming to mind are fundamentally wrong. After all, we all know that life is just a game of different levels of difficulty. But be calm, because "fools are lucky" — you will get out of all the adventures, taking with you lessons that no one even suspects.</string>
    <string name="taro11">Justice! This term sounds like a fantasy game! Which is about honesty, fair law, and a life where everything happens according to prescribed rules. But isn\'t it funny that reality often steals these rules and hides them under its couch? And so, as if by magic, causes and effects appear, and life lessons for all of us become a true find for seekers of justice!</string>
    <string name="taro12">Love, harmony, partnership, choice! How wonderful it is when the opportunity appears on the horizon to be in the arms of an ideal partner or to choose between two identical appetizers on the menu.… This card promises you something important — maybe just throw away your old socks, or maybe something much more grandiose, like who to be — a hobbit or a superhero? Don\'t forget, temptation only whispers in your ear that the path of least resistance is indeed the best choice. Don\'t fall for the tricks of the cards, choose wisely... or just order a pizza!</string>
    <string name="taro13">Willpower, creativity, manifestation — it almost sounds like an advertising slogan for another personal development training, doesn\'t it? This card, of course, promises you that your wishes and dreams will come true, as if you have a magic wand. When it falls to you, you should immediately fall into euphoria: "Hooray! I have aspirations, and now I\'m definitely going to make my dreams come true!" But you do remember that just "wishing" is half the battle, and the rest depends solely on you.</string>
    <string name="taro14">Balance is the greatest miracle of our time! Moderation, good health, cooperation... yes, it\'s every person\'s dream, a complete idyll! However, it is worth remembering that moderation is not just a cool concept, but a stumbling block in our mental practice. In any difficult situation, our inner voice whispers, "React!"  But who will try to find a way out when there is an opportunity to "solve" everything at the touch of a button? So we remain on the verge between miracles and catastrophes, I hope one day to finally get to a bright future!</string>
    <string name="taro15">We all like to stew in our own cocktail of anxiety and delusions. And, of course, we trust our imagination, as if it were the most reliable compass. Not noticing that our fears spread out before us like the red carpet at the premiere of another blockbuster movie. After all, in the end, don\'t you want to get rid of what binds you? Or do you prefer to stay in your cozy delusions, like a cat in a box?</string>
    <string name="taro16">Happiness, success, optimism, truth – this card is like a funny clown at the celebration of life, promising satisfaction. Don\'t worry if you\'re having a hard time right now; after all, the Sun will really show you its vertical appearance. Are you aiming for the bright side? Why not? We can always make "lemonade from lemons", although sometimes it seems that we just get a sour mixture, right?</string>
    <string name="taro17">This card symbolizes strength, courage, compassion, and focus. It sounds like a call to heroism in a world full of inaction! You\'re just like a "Superman" in a robe, ready to move mountains! But wait, have you been told that strength is not only a graceful dance, but also a constant clash with harsh reality? And don\'t forget, true strength isn\'t always about pounding your fist on the table—sometimes it\'s just about surviving the chaos.</string>
    <string name="taro18">The person this card hints at is the true supreme lawman! He\'s like a hyperactive teacher explaining how best to follow the rules that he himself came up with. His whole life is an endless lecture about the “right thing.” He is quite suitable for the role of a mentor who knows how to arrange the lives of others.</string>
    <string name="taro19">Intuition, divine femininity — sounds like the name of a therapeutic session for vultures tired of life. And when you get a High Priestess, it\'s like a roulette wheel: "Now you will have an exciting journey into the inner world!" It\'s time to learn, because, of course, you haven\'t learned anything in your entire life. Listen to your intuition — yes, the one that tells you to choose the next episode on Netflix instead of reading a smart book.</string>
    <string name="taro20">Hope, renewal, creativity and inspiration are the main set of optimists. This card means that you have been through something "difficult" - maybe through another drama or a truly exciting event, which you can now nostalgic for with a smile. When we go through pain, it\'s like we lose everything bright, but maybe something good is still waiting for us around the corner? And in a few days or years, we will sincerely laugh at the "failure of the century.".</string>
    <string name="taro21">Life decides to challenge you, and it seems like it\'s time for you to return from fantasy to reality. Complete destruction, where instead of a red carpet, glass and charcoal were laid out for you. Losses and defeats are quite a painful process, but it\'s up to you to decide what it will lead to: the abyss of despair or a bright future. If we decided to update the design of this map a little: a falling plane would be an ideal metaphor — this is exactly what our hopes look like at the moment of collision with the realities of life. So before embarking on an exciting journey to new beginnings, ask yourself: are you ready to face the truth and let go of your illusions?</string>
    <string name="taro22">Harmony, completion, integration — just a bouquet of words for the successful completion of another exciting journey! Yes, this road was difficult, littered with "difficulties" and "challenges." And finally, you\'re sitting on the throne of your achievements, as if it were so easy! Those "seeds" that you "sowed" have now, of course, blossomed into beautiful flowers.… But don\'t forget - the higher you fly, the more painful it is to fall.</string>
    <string name="taro1M">If the cards had slogans, the chariot would have it - "Take everything except modesty!" Your success train has already started and, as they say, give -take, beat - run. However, this card is also a symbol of overcoming obstacles, where determination, concentration and willpower turn into your personal superpowers. Feel this motivation, ambition and control! But be careful not to lose your way: life is such a bore without a healthy dose of fear and doubt!</string>
    <string name="taro2M">Feeling depressed, helpless, and insignificant? It\'s like a best friend, always there, as well as self-doubt.
 Agree, anxiety and introspection are a real trend that has taken the first place in our internal rating! Now is the perfect time to think about whether your actions are consistent with your values or are they just a smelly compromise?
 Question from Dostoevsky: are you a trembling creature or do you have the right?!
 Take the time to get to know yourself before turning on this "running man" mode again.
 And don\'t forget that
 "You made your own wheel
 "And I made a runner squirrel costume for myself,
 So that there are 24 hours a day
 Chasing a ghostly prize with all your might" - Noize MC</string>
    <string name="taro3M">Resistance to change is, throughout the ages, our old acquaintance. The fear of new beginnings feels like pepper in the mouth of any optimist. Risk, excitement, new beginnings? No way — let\'s better cherish the most dysfunctional patterns that we keep so carefully in our heads. The Death Card is like a mockery of fate: yes, one chapter ends, but do not rush to remove the old notes — they will still be needed when you start to stir up failures over and over again. And it\'s up to you to decide which page will be next - a new chapter? Good stability? Or just a new batch of old rusty junk?</string>
    <string name="taro4M">Overcoming addiction and restoring strength — it sounds like we\'re talking about something fabulous and fantasy. Independence and freedom — wow! But let\'s not forget that here lies the temptation of the most sacred illusion.: how quickly you can forget everything... and go back to suffering. The devil is your best friend, isn\'t he? Although you\'re supposed to be in control of your life, he\'s happy to tell you your habits. Even sports and social media turn into his insidious tentacles if you do not follow the measure. But don\'t lose heart! The main thing is to keep a sense of humor and redirect your desires to something more important, such as choosing the volume of your suffering.</string>
    <string name="taro5M">There is excessive control hanging over you — as if there is not enough pedagogical approach in our apartment. This person sacrifices his time to create rules that can only be useful in preaching. And the knowledge he conveys is just a storehouse of simple truths, known to everyone, but presented with such pomp that it seems as if they had just been unearthed from ancient scrolls. Hooray, your butt can sleep peacefully on the sofa, because your father is looming over us. And the fact that he may not be what you dreamed of is that you made this choice in the first place.</string>
    <string name="taro6M">The Empress with the crown seems to hint: look for beauty and happiness in your life. But it seems that she forgot to clarify that for this search you may have to throw feathers on your head and wave a magic wand to at least catch something. \n
                        Keep looking, dear ones! Suddenly, behind the coincidence of coincidences, there will be that same spark of joy in the very depths of your overgrown soul.</string>,
    <string name="taro7M">The wheel of Fortune suddenly decided to turn around and show you the other side, as if we all miss our useless problems. But don\'t worry - it\'s the wheel, and indeed fate itself! Now you can proudly claim that "It wasn't "I came up with the shit, but that\'s what the cards said."
 But, but! Not personal fucking, but working out karma" - Aster X Make your dreams come true, as if you have the strength for it, and you have defenders in heaven. Remember, there is nothing to be afraid of – everything will go on as usual thanks to divine intervention and a secret plan that no one knows about.</string>
    <string name="taro8M">Dissatisfaction, stagnation, lack of visible ways out of the situation – how nice it is to exchange precious minutes of life for introspection, where one\'s own fear and self-loathing become a favorite pastime. The Hanged Man is that magical "waiting card" where time stops and we make a good face at a bad game. We may not enjoy this limbo, but who would turn down the opportunity to sit around drinking the elixir of fear of life? After all, isn\'t it wonderful to sacrifice your dreams and connections by staying put?</string>
    <string name="taro9M">Loneliness and paranoia framed in porcelain sadness, wallowing in illusory fears... You\'re fading like old seafood in the heat. But how fascinating is one\'s own isolation! After all, falling into paralysis with the simultaneous exposure to the deepest emotional analysis and introspection is a true art! Just don\'t dive too deep, or you\'ll drown. The hermit is just a joke of nature! It symbolizes the wisdom gained by meeting with the most distant and no less lonely corners of your soul. The motto of this card is: "The closer to yourself, the further away from the whole world!" It is very convenient, by the way! But do you really need it?</string>
    <string name="taro10M">You are impulsive and childish. And instead of solving problems, you use them as a stand for your visibility of activity. Your life is full of disorder, and the desire to please society turns into a comedy performance where you are the main loser. But be calm, because "fools are lucky" — you will get out of all the adventures, taking with you lessons that no one even suspects.</string>
    <string name="taro11M">Injustice walks without shame, and responsibility runs away from its obligations, hiding in cozy pools of lies. Karma is having fun celebrating your illusions! And if suddenly someone has hurt you, don\'t worry - justice may just be stuck in traffic, but in the end… It\'s supposed to come, isn\'t it? Or maybe he\'s just not going to at all?</string>
    <string name="taro12M">Imbalance and disharmony... How quickly we are sliding into the abyss of doubt! Based on this, do you panic, not knowing who to trust today — the cat who is always there? Or someone who promises to lead to wonderland, but may just turn out to be a dubious taxi driver? Don\'t forget, temptation only whispers in your ear that the path of least resistance is indeed the best choice. Don\'t fall for the tricks of the cards, choose wisely... or just order a pizza!</string>
    <string name="taro13M">Manipulation and illusions—oh, yes, it already sounds like castle-building skills. So arm yourself with determination and willpower — just don\'t forget to bring at least a little skepticism with you. After all, magic alone won\'t help you with the realities of life, especially if your dreams involve something more significant than just going to the store for eclair.</string>
    <string name="taro14M">When it comes to inverted balance, this is real entertainment. Haste, risky behavior – just not to get bored against the background of perfect harmony!Avoid extreme situations, because you don\'t need any drama, right? However, sometimes it\'s just necessary to walk on the "knife\'s edge"! In any difficult situation, our inner voice whispers, "React!"  But who will try to find a way out when there is an opportunity to "solve" everything at the touch of a button? So we remain on the verge between miracles and catastrophes, I hope one day to finally get to a bright future!</string>
    <string name="taro15M">Try shining your inner flashlight a little to banish the illusions. Life is full of unremarkable secrets that we don\'t even know about. And yes, it might be worth stopping wishful thinking and facing the truth.. After all, in the end, don\'t you want to get rid of what binds you? Or do you prefer to stay in your cozy delusions, like a cat in a box?</string>
    <string name="taro16M">Life is not always sweet like honey. Well, if we talk about life lessons, then they can be perceived as uninvited teachers who have not even chosen their subject. But despite all this, let\'s be optimistic, because "difficult times don\'t last forever"... until a new difficulty begins.</string>
    <string name="taro17M">Self-doubt, weakness, rude emotions... Oh, how cheerful! And how nice it is to hear that you have the opportunity to keep a positive attitude, even when there is a zombie apocalypse around! It\'s funny, just like the certainty that sitting in eternal traffic jams, you can always stay calm and think logically. Let\'s be honest: losing patience is a temporary phenomenon that no one is immune from. And don\'t forget, true strength isn\'t always about pounding your fist on the table—sometimes it\'s just about surviving the chaos.</string>
    <string name="taro18M">The inverted Priest symbolizes the mask of a strict teacher, under which a hypocritical moralist hides. Such a person will devalue everything he touches and does not do. "All bastards, I am D\'Artagnan alone" - this is his true nature, behind which lies only the emptiness of spiritual sorrow.</string>
    <string name="taro19M">Slow down, you have a cache of wisdom in your closet somewhere and you just didn\'t have time to open it. Why make decisions or act when you can replay all the old grievances and complexes in your head? Of course, getting more knowledge sounds attractive, but don\'t forget — there are other activities in this world besides introspection. So relax and let your intuition guide you to new heights... or to the next cup of tea.</string>
    <string name="taro20M">Hopelessness, creative block, boredom, and, of course, your favorite focus on negativity. The universe blesses us abundantly, and we continue to attract the "desired" through our cherished thoughts. It\'s worth remembering that all troubles are not the end of the world, but just an opportunity to build something "better." Open your heart, realize your inner strength, and the market for fleeting, and perhaps not so much, joys awaits you ahead.</string>
    <string name="taro21M">Life decides to challenge you, and it seems like it\'s time for you to return from fantasy to reality. Complete destruction, where instead of a red carpet, glass and charcoal were laid out for you. Losses and defeats are quite a painful process, but it\'s up to you to decide what it will lead to: the abyss of despair or a bright future. If we decided to update the design of this map a little: a falling plane would be an ideal metaphor — this is exactly what our hopes look like at the moment of collision with the realities of life. So before embarking on an exciting journey to new beginnings, ask yourself: are you ready to face the truth and let go of your illusions?</string>
    <string name="taro22M">Every time you think you\'ve finally achieved what you want, here it is—an empty space left over from your "successes." But don\'t worry, there\'s still plenty of time for "achievements" in this new round! Please don\'t forget: this is just another stage of your "journey". As they say, "everything passes and it will pass."</string>
    <string name="taroH1">The Chariot</string>
    <string name="taroH2">Court</string>
    <string name="taroH3">Death</string>
    <string name="taroH4">Devil</string>
    <string name="taroH5">Emperor</string>
    <string name="taroH6">The Empress</string>
    <string name="taroH7">Fortune</string>
    <string name="taroH8">The Hanged Man</string>
    <string name="taroH9">Hermit</string>
    <string name="taroH10">Jester</string>
    <string name="taroH11">Justice</string>
    <string name="taroH12">The lovers</string>
    <string name="taroH13">The Magician</string>
    <string name="taroH14">Moderation</string>
    <string name="taroH15">Moon</string>
    <string name="taroH16">The sun</string>
    <string name="taroH17">Power</string>
    <string name="taroH18">The High Priest</string>
    <string name="taroH19">The High Priestess</string>
    <string name="taroH20">Star</string>
    <string name="taroH21">Tower</string>
    <string name="taroH22">World</string>
    <string name="dndH">The Gods of Randomness favor you!</string>
    <string name="dndH1">OOPS!!!</string>
    <string name="methods">RESULT</string>
    <string name="dnd0">You have today + 0 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd1">You have today + 1 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd2">You have today + 2 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd3">You have today + 3 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd4">You have today + 4 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd5">You have today + 5 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd6">You have today + 6 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd7">You have today + 7 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd8">You have today + 8 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd9">You have today + 9 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd10">You have today + 10 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd11">You have today + 11 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd12">You have today + 12 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd13">You have today + 13 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd14">You have today + 14 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd15">You have today + 15 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd16">You have today + 16 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd17">You have today + 17 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd18">You have today + 18 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd19">You have today + 19 to luck</string>
    <string name="dnd20">You have today + 20 to luck</string>
    <string name="onas1">Greetings!</string>
    <string name="onas2">My name is Dylan and I am a novice application developer.</string>
    <string name="onas3">I really hope you enjoyed my first app :)</string>
    <string name="onas4">I would like to say a special thanks to Risa Swan, who drew all the pictures for this application.</string>
    <string name="onas5">You can support the project on boosty:</string>
    <string name="onas6">I\'m waiting at my place, there are a lot of interesting things there.:</string>
    <string name="listH1">Enter the advantages</string>
    <string name="listH2">Enter the cons</string>
    <string name="quH1">What happens if you do this?</string>
    <string name="quH2">What happens if you don\'t?</string>
    <string name="quH3">What won\'t happen if you do that?</string>
    <string name="quH4">What won\'t happen if you don\'t do it?</string>
    <string name="mess1">It\'s up to you, of course, but we don\'t think you should do that! \n The disadvantages of your decision outweigh it. Find more advantages in your planned actions or direct your energy in the other direction.</string>
    <string name="mess2">What are you waiting for and thinking about? Go ahead!\n The pros outweigh all the cons of your solution. Forward to the victory of communism! (well, not only him)</string>
    <string name="mess3">Even artificial intelligence finds it difficult to give you advice. \n The cons and pros of your solution are equal. So come up with something else that will help swing your weight in the right direction. \n And don\'t forget that you came here ALREADY KNOWING the answer you want to get.</string>
    <string name="errorL">Please fill out all the sheets!</string>
    <string name="errorF1">Please fill in the rating!</string>
    <string name="errorF2">Please enter the item!</string>
    <string name="butAdd">ADD</string>
    <string name="placIn">Enter the item</string>
    <string name="textIn1">How important is this point to you?</string>
    <string name="textIn2">1 is not important at all, 5 is very important</string>
    <string name="textIn3">Importance selected:</string>
    <string name="result">The result!</string>
</resources>